(Page:)I see.
(Howard:)Well, it's good to know, when
I need you guys, I can always
(Howard:)count on you to step up
and ruin everything.
(Leonard:)I feel awful.
(Raj:)Ah, me, too.
(Leonard:)To tell you the truth,
(Leonard:)I thought if anyone was going to
(Leonard:)screw things up for Howard,
it'd be Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Well, your expectations
have been subverted.
(Sheldon:)Aha.
(Leonard:)What are you doing up?
(Sheldon:)Sleep eludes me, Leonard.
(Leonard:)Really?
(Leonard:)Maybe sleep has met you before.
(Sheldon:)Mockery?
(Sheldon:)That's all you have to offer?
(Leonard:)I'm sorry. Why can't you sleep?
(Sheldon:)Who knows?
(Sheldon:)I haven't watched
any scary movies recently.
(Sheldon:)I'm no longer obsessing
over why the predicted mass
(Sheldon:)of the quantum vacuum
has little effect
(Sheldon:)on the expansion
of the universe.
(Sheldon:)And it's been weeks since I took
that accidental sip of Red Bull.